本∶简直无法相信!真是无法相信,
Ben: I can't believe it!
劳拉林居然会在情人节放我鸽子.
I just can't believe it; Laura-Lynn standing me up, me!And on Valentine's Day.
开萝尔∶本,如果劳拉林让你这么可怜兮兮的,
Carol: Ben, why do you keep going with Laura-Lynn if she makes you so
你为什么要继续和她约会呢?
miserable?I mean, I don't mean to sound judgmental but it makes you look
我不是要批判什么,只是感觉你现在像只疯狗一样.
like a pathetic dork.
本∶至少我没有跟公司的女孩子出去闲荡,
Ben: At least I'm not hanging out with the girls from the office,
去看我们到底能吃多少.
seeing how much we can eat.
如果劳拉林在5分钟内还不来的话,那我就要把这些巧克力都吞下去了.
If Laura's not here in five minutes,
妈妈,
I'm sucking the middles out of these babies.
异性之间的对抗什么时候会停止呀?
Mom, when do struggles with the opposite sex stop?
麦琪∶死之后.
Maggie: At the funeral home.
本∶妈妈,你为什么不租一个人接你去和爸爸约会呢?
Ben: Shouldn't you have hired a lift for your date with Dad?
麦琪∶你是说那个在情人节的晚上,迟到一个小时,
Maggie: You mean with the man who is an hour late on Valentine's Day and
并且没有任何电话的男人?
hasn't called?
本∶妈妈,不要伤心.要不要和我一起吃巧克力?
Ben: Ah, don't feel bad, Mom.Wanna help me suck these chocolates?
杰森∶嘿,大家好.对不起我迟到了一会.麦琪,你没有生气吧?
Jason: Hey, hi everybody, sorry I'm a little late.Maggie, you're not mad, are you?
麦琪∶我相信你肯定是有原因的.
Maggie: Well, I'm sure you have a really good reason.
你可能是被你的病人的紧急情况所牵跘了,或是在路上堵车了,
You probably got tied up with a patient in emergency or got caught in
或其他别的什么原因.
traffic, or something.
杰森∶哈哈,事实上我只是忘记了我们今天晚上要出去吃饭.
Jason: Ha ha, actually I just forgot we were going out for dinner tonight.
是不是很好笑?
Isn't that funny?
麦琪∶你忘记了我们的情人节晚餐,还说有趣!
Maggie: You forgot our Valentine's dinner, and that's funny!
杰森∶但是当我记起来的时候,我就记得买花了.
Jason: Well, but when I remembered I remembered flowers.
麦琪∶你从哪里弄来的?第7个出口的驶出坡道?
Maggie: Where'd you get these?The off ramp at exit seven?
杰森∶决不是..是第9出口.
Jason: Absolutely not...exit nine.
麦琪∶我去拿外套.
Maggie: I'll get my coat.
迈克∶嘿爸爸,你可以借给我60元吗?
Mike: Hey Dad, can I borrow sixty Bucks?
杰森∶什么,不说"嗨,爸爸,爸爸你好吗","很高兴见到你"之类的,就只有一个嘿?
Jason: What, no, hi Dad, how are you Dad, nice to see you Dad?
迈克∶每次我那样说的时候你都说,
Mike: Well, every time I say that you say, how much.
多少.
I'm just trying to save time here.
我现在只是想节省时间而已.我和凯特有约会,
OK, listen, I've got a date with Kate tonight and everything's got to
我想让一切都完美一点.
be just perfect.
杰森∶嘿,你最好带她去时时乐.
Jason: Oh, hey, you better be taking her to the Sizzler.
迈克∶爸爸,我是在和她约会,我还没和她结婚呢.
Mike: Dad, I'm dating Kate, I'm not married to her.
本∶至少他给凯特买了漂亮的花.
Ben: At least he got her nice flowers.
迈克∶本,别越帮越忙.
Mike: Ben, don't help me here.
杰森∶迈克,迈克,
Jason: Mike, Mike, Mike,
迈克,我借你钱,你把花给我.
I'll lend you the money if you exchange bouquets with me.
迈克∶爸爸,要不这样吧?你觉得我们一人一半怎么样?
Mike: Ah, well, err...how about this?Dad how about if we split the bouquet...
杰森∶说了等于白说.
Jason: You get nothing.
迈克∶过开心点.
Mike: Enjoy.
劳拉林∶我们走,本,
Laura-Lynn: Let's go Ben, my mom's in the car waiting.
我妈妈正在车里等我们呢.西维尔医生你好,迈克你好.
Oh, hello Doctor Seaver, hi Mike.
迈克∶你好.
Mike: Hi.
杰森∶你好.
Jason: Hi.
本∶让我穿好我的外套.
Ben: Let me finish getting my coat on.
劳拉林∶你为什么还没有准备好?你知道我们已经迟到了?
Laura-Lynn: Why aren't you ready?Do you know we're late?
本:劳拉林,我不知道你为什么对我喊,
Ben: Look Laura, I don't know why you're yelling at me,
是你迟到了.也许我们就不该约会.
you're the one who's late; maybe we shouldn't even go on this stupid date.
劳拉林∶本,你还从来没有对我这么大声说过话...
Laura-Lynn: Ben, you've never been forceful with me before...I like it.
我喜欢.站直了.
Stand up straight.
本∶是亲爱的.
Ben: Yes dear.
麦琪∶迈克,你要带凯特去哪里吃晚餐?
Maggie: So, where are you taking Kate for dinner?
迈克∶只是一个小的法国餐馆...La Village.
Mike: It's just some little French place...La Village.
麦琪和杰森∶La Village!!
Maggie and Jason: La Village!!
杰森∶迈克,你不是要求婚吧?
Jason: Mike, you're not proposing, are you?
迈克∶不是.
Mike: No.
杰森:那可是是个很不错的地方.你从来没有带朱莉去过.
Jason: Well you know, it's just that's quite a place.You never took Julie there.
麦琪∶哼,你也没带我去过.
Maggie: Huh, you never took me there.
迈克∶不过就是一顿晚餐而已嘛.
Mike: Guys, come on, it's just a dinner.
杰森:听到了么,你儿子可不在乎钱.
Jason: You hear that Jason, he's your son and he's not afraid to spend money.
迈克:当然,那是我的钱.
Mike: Oh sure because it's my money.
杰森∶哦,对了,
Jason: And by the way, these are your real flowers,
麦琪,这些才是要送给你的花,
the others were just a joke, Maggie.
刚才那个不过是和你开个玩笑罢了.没有一个正常的男人会送那样的花给女人.
No man in his right mind would give a woman those.
麦琪∶迈克尔,你能不能帮我把花插在水中?
Maggie: Michael, will you put these in water for me please.
迈克∶没问题.
Mike: You got it.
杰森∶我们走吧?不要浪费时间了.
Jason: Shall we?Don't wait up.
麦琪∶哦,亲爱的,你要带我去哪里?
Maggie: Oh, honey, where are you taking me?
杰森∶我想给你一个惊喜.
Jason: Well, I want it to be a surprise.
麦琪∶我以前没去过?
Maggie: What, I haven't been there before?
杰森∶啊,无可奉告.
Jason: Ah, no comment.
麦琪∶我是不是穿的太华丽了?
Maggie: Am I over-dressed?
杰森∶有点.
Jason: For something.
大A1∶你好.
Big Al: Howdy.
杰森∶呃...你好.
Mike: Err...howdy.
开萝尔的同事:我们跟开萝尔一起过情人节.
Carol's colleague: Err...we're here for Carol's valentine-less Valentine's Day party
Big Al: Oh, we're from Carol's office...except for her, she's my mom
Big Al's Mom: Nice to meet you, Carol.Albert's told me so much about you
迈克∶开萝尔,你的同事们来了!
Mike: Carol, the A list is here!
开萝尔:嗨!
Carol: Hi!
迈克∶让放帮你把这些放进水中.
Mike: Let me put those in water for you.
开萝尔∶我希望大家都带了浪漫的电影.我的是租来的,窗外有蓝天.
Carol: I hope everybody brought a romantic movie.I rented, A Room With A View.
同事∶我带来的是,军官与绅士.
Colleagues: Ooh!And I got, An Officer and A Gentleman.
Big Al: Aww!bam And I got, Samson and Delilah, with Victor Mateaux
we should all have breasts like that man.
侍者∶欢迎来到La Village,先生,
Waiter: Welcome to La Village, enjoy your meal Monsieur,
请享用你的晚餐,小姐,祝你有个好胃口.
and bon appetit Mademoiselle.
凯特∶迈克,我跟你说我很想来这个地方的时候,
Kate: You know, Mike, when I told you I always wanted to try this place,
并没有暗示说要你带我来.
I wasn't hinting that you'd bring me here.
迈克∶是的,你就是.
Mike: Yes you were.
凯特∶你肯定我是.
Kate: You bet I was.
迈克∶你想吃什么就点什么,因为...
Mike: OK, now look, I want you to order anything you want because...
一个汤要5美元!!啊!我怎么说话这么像我爸了.
Five Dollars for soup!!Ah!I'm sounding like my dad.
凯特∶每个看上去都不错.
Kate: Everything looks so good.
迈克∶恩,是的.你以前从来没有来过吗?
Mike: Mmm, sure does.So...err...you've never been here before?
凯特∶没有.
Kate: No.
迈克∶说到约会...
Mike: Well, speaking of dating...
凯特∶谁在说到在说约会?
Kate: Who's speaking of dating?
迈克∶啊,我在说.
Mike: Ah,
凯特∶什么时候?
Kate: When?
迈克:我在说约会.我们在说什么?
Mike: Well, when I said speaking of dating.What were we talking about?
凯特∶约会.
Kate: Errm...dating.
迈克∶我很高兴你能提出来,凯特,
Mike: You know, I'm glad you brought that up.
我一直在想...
You know, Kate, I've been thinking...
凯特∶每当你认真的时候,就特别可爱.
Kate: You are so adorable when you're trying to be serious.
迈克:真的?鬼脸一个.好,说到约会……
Mike: Really?You know, death haunts me.OK, now getting back to dating...
凯特∶再次.
Kate: Again.
迈克∶嗨,是你提起来的.
Mike: Hey, you brought it up.
凯特∶因此,约会怎么样?
Kate: So, what about dating?
迈克∶我们现在已经约会了几个星期了吧.
Mike: Well, errm...well we've been doing it for a few weeks now.
凯特∶是吧,我想是,哼?
Kate: Yeah, I guess we have, huh?
迈克∶对,有6个星期了.
Mike: Yeah, it's been six weeks.
凯特∶六个星期再加3天.
Kate: Six weeks and three days.
迈克∶我,我,我,从来没与其他的女孩子约会过.
Mike: Yeah, and I...I...I personally haven't dated anyone else.
凯特∶噢呼.
Kate: Uh hu.
迈克∶我本来...个别地.
Mike: Yeah, and I could have...personally.
凯特:啊?
Kate: Oh?
迈克∶凯特,你有别的什么要跟我说的吗?
Mike: Kate, is there anything else you'd like to say here?
凯特∶没有.
Kate: No.
迈克∶你喜欢使我发狂,是吗?
Mike: You love driving me nuts, don't you?
凯特∶那是我第二喜欢做的事情.
Kate: It's my second favorite thing to do.
迈克∶好了,好了.
Mike: OK, alright, alright.
凯特∶迈克,我也没有与其他人约会,或者,
Kate: Mike, I haven't dated anyone else, either, and I haven't wanted to.
我并不想.你知道吗,我觉得我现在过的真的很开心.
You know, I'm really happy with the way things are right now.
迈克∶你的意思是说,你喜欢做我的女朋友?
Mike: So, you're saying...you kind of like being my girlfriend.
凯特∶是的,我!作你的女朋友.
Kate: I love being your girlfriend.
迈克∶爱!我是不是可以认为...
Mike: Love!Well, does this mean...
凯特∶你认为怎么样?
Kate: What do you think?
开萝尔∶凯特,我真的需要知道你的想法,因为我知道我自己是怎么想的.
Mike: Look, Kate, I really need to know what you think because I know what I think.
凯特∶好的!
Kate: Yeah!
朱莉:我是朱莉,今晚为你服务.迈克!
Julie: Bonjour, my name is Julie and I'll be your waitress this evening.Mike!
(回到朱莉离开迈克的时候)
(Back in time to when Julie left Mike)
迈克∶我是迈克尔西维尔,我和我的未婚妻约好1点钟在这里见牧师的.
Mike: Hi my name's Michael Seaver and my fiancé and I are meeting the minister here at one o' clock.
女人∶西维尔先生,有封信是给你的.
Woman: Mr.Seaver, yes, well this was left for you.
迈克∶谢谢你.
Mike: Oh, thank you.
朱莉的信:亲爱的迈克,
Letter from Julie: Dear Mike, by the time you read this I'll be on a plane,
当你读这封信的时候,
and I've never written a letter like this before,
我已经在飞机上了.
so I don't know how to start.
我一直在想我们两个人的婚事,
I've been thinking about you and me and marriage; Mike,
我很不放心.
I've got so many questions and I've got so many doubts.
可能我太疯狂了.
Maybe I'm crazy or just scared out of my mind.
我不知道,
I don't know, maybe it's cold feet, but all I know right now is,
但是我先在不能.
I can't go through with this.
迈克∶啊;朱莉!朱莉!你好!
Mike: Ah, Julie!Julie!Hi!
朱莉∶你好迈克.
Julie: Hi Mike.
迈克∶你是女服务员,在这么高级的地方.
Mike: So, you err...you...ah...you're a waitress, here at this very place.
朱莉∶是的.
Julie: Yeah.
迈克∶哦,你想坐下来恶劣?你不能,因为你是女侍者.
Mike: Yeah, oh, do you wanna sit?You can't, you're a waitress.
朱莉∶我是.
Julie: I am.
迈克∶我不知道你在这里.
Mike: I didn't know that.
朱莉与迈克∶世界真小.
Julie and Mike: Small world.
凯特∶我在等有人解释一下呢.
Kate: I was waiting for someone to say that.
迈克∶哦,哦,呃...朱莉...,
Mike: Oh, oh, right...err...Julie...Costello, this is err...Kate!Kate!
这是凯特!凯特!凯特麦克旦尼尔.我知道你的姓.
Kate McDonnell.I knew that.
凯特∶你好朱莉.
Kate: Hi Julie.
朱莉∶你好凯特.
Julie: Hi Kate.
凯特∶朱莉,我们要再多看一会菜单.
Kate: Julie, we need a few more minutes with the menu.
朱莉∶当然,当然可以.
Julie: Of course, of course you do.
迈克∶对,还有多看几分钟...菜单.
Mike: Yeah, just a couple more minutes with...with the menu.
朱莉∶慢慢来.
Julie: Take your time.
迈克∶哦,我刚才只是头脑一片空白.我知道你的名字,好吗?我就像知道我自己的名字一样记得你的.我还可以拼写出来呢.
Mike: Oh, look, I just drew a blank there.I know your name, OK?I know it like my own.I can even spell it.
凯特∶那是朱莉.
Kate: So, that was Julie.
迈克∶啊...
Mike: Ah...
凯特∶朱莉.
Kate: The Julie.
迈克∶我知道我跟你说起过关于她的事情,
Mike: I know that I've told you a little bit about her,
但是你要相信的是,
but you just have to understand that this is the first time that we've
这是我们俩从我取消我们的婚礼后的第一次见面.
even seen each other since...well since, since I called our wedding off.
凯特∶迈克,也许我们应该离开.
Kate: Mike, maybe we should go.
迈克∶不用,凯特,不用!不,
Mike: No, Kate, no!No, no, no, I'm fine, I'm fine, I can handle this.
不,不,我很好,我很好,我可以处理好的.
OK, look, why don't we just look over these menus, OK?
我们为什么不看看菜单呢?哦,阿尔弗雷多罗马诺,看上去还不错.
Oh wow, Alfredo Romano , that sounds great.
凯特∶迈克,那是厨师的名字.
Kate: Mike, that's the chef's name.
我只是觉得如果我们换个地方会吃的轻松点.
Look, I just think we'd be more comfortable eating at another restaurant.
迈克∶听着朱莉...我是说凯特!不用,不必担心.
Mike: Look Julie...I mean Kate!Look, no, no, don't worry.
谢谢你的体谅,但是,我很好.我能处理好的.
I appreciate that but I'm fine.I can handle this.
凯特∶我不是为你考虑,我是为我自己着想.
Kate: I wasn't thinking about you, I was thinking about me.
迈克∶这和你有什么关系?
Mike: What have you got to do with this?
凯特∶迈克!我不喜欢这样的情形.
Kate: Mike!This isn't exactly a pleasant situation for me.
迈克∶哦,哦,
Mike: Oh, oh, oh!
哦!
You mean you having dinner with your new boyfriend and being served by
你是说当你和你的新男朋友用餐的时候,他以前的未婚妻在一旁伺候着的情形让你觉得不开心.
his former fiancé is not a pleasant situation.
凯特:也许在加利福尼亚.迈克,
Kate: Maybe in California.
你得承认你有点紧张.
Come on Mike, admit it, you're a little uneasy yourself.
迈克∶对,我承认;但是那是在开始的时候,
Mike: OK, I admit it; I was at first,
现在我已经平静下来了,我也准备好和你共进美妙的晚餐了.
but now I am calm and I am ready for a great dinner, OK?
我们把她叫来准备点餐吧,好吗?
I'm just going to tell what's her name that we are ready to order, alright?
劳拉林∶劳拉,你妈妈正在那里呢!
Laura-Lynn: Ben, you're a whole different you tonight; so commanding, so manly.
本:再见.
Ben: See ya.
劳拉林:劳拉,,你妈妈在这儿.
Laura-Lynn: Laura, you're mom's right there!
劳拉林∶本,我也是个有需要的女人.晚安,本杰明.
Laura-Lynn: Ben, I'm a woman with needs.Good night, Benjamin.
本∶奥,怎么回事 ?
Ben: Wow.What's the matter?
开萝尔的同事∶他回来了...理查德奇尔回来了.
Carol's colleague: He came back...Richard Gear came back.
大A1∶我知道...我知道.
Big Al: I knew I...I knew it.
开萝尔∶他真的爱她的.
Carol: He really loved her.
本∶那个女士的舌头都要掉出来了.
Ben: That other lady's tongues hanging out.
开萝尔∶我们知道,本.你出去!
Carol: We know that, Ben.Will you get out!
Big Al: Do you wanna watch the bedroom scene again in slow-mo
开萝尔∶哦,已经是最后一部电影了!
Carol: Well, that was the last movie!
开萝尔的同事∶这是我过的最快乐的一个情人节!.
Carol's colleague: This is the best valentine's day I ever had
开萝尔∶我很抱歉.
Carol: I am so sorry.
迈克∶哇,很棒的晚餐,是吗?嘿,真的是为我准备的;法国人真的太会做饭了.我打赌他们能把任何东西做成调味料.凯特,谢谢你,我会另外找个时间再来请你喝咖啡.
Mike: Wow!Boy, some dinner, huh?Hey, that settles it for me; the French can cook.You know, I bet they could turn anything into a sauce.Ah hey, well thanks anyway Kate, but I'm gonna stop in for coffee another time.
凯特∶我没有让你请.
Kate: I didn't ask you.
迈克∶哦!
Mike: Oh!
凯特∶事实上,自从我们离开餐厅以来,我一句话都没有说过.
Kate: In fact, I haven't said a word since we left the restaurant.
托尼∶真地?
Mike: Really?
凯特∶事实上,自从与朱莉不期而遇以后,我们都很少说话.
Kate: In fact hardly a word since we bumped into Judy.
迈克∶啊...是..
Mike: Ah...it's
凯特∶我知道,朱莉.我还注意到,她的名字一直挂在你的嘴边.
Kate: Ah, I know, Julie.I notice, her name's on the tip of your tongue.
迈克∶别这样,凯特.
Mike: Look, come on, Kate, I've apologized for that a hundred times.
我已经为这个道歉了几百次了.那你还想要我道歉多少次,才肯罢休?
I mean, how many more do you need?
凯特:我只是想告诉你,
Kate: I'll let you know.
我都已经忘记了.
Mike, let's just forget this whole night ever happened, OK?
迈克∶什么晚上?晚安凯特,晚点给你打电话.
Mike: What night?Good night then Kate, I'll call you later.
凯特∶你为什么会有这样的行为?
Kate: Why are you acting like this?
迈克∶什么行为,凯特?
Mike: Like what, Kate?
凯特∶像有秘密的人的行为.
Kate: Like someone who has a secret.
迈克∶好了,放过我吧.
Mike: Oh, come on, give me a break.
凯特∶放过我吧!!我是说你的举止看上去让人觉得,你因为结束了那段关系而深感抱歉.
Kate: Give me a break!I mean, you're acting like you're sorry you ended that
relationship
迈克∶不是这样的.
Mike: Well, that is not true.
凯特∶迈克,请你跟我坦白!
Kate: Mike, be honest with me!
迈克∶坦白!坦白,你想要坦白,好,我告诉你,不是我甩了她,而是她甩了我!
Mike: Ho...honest!honest, you want honest, OK.Alright, I didn't dump her!I'm the one who got dumped.
凯特∶什么?
Kate: What?
迈克∶不是我取消婚礼的,是她.对不起,我跟你说谎了,
Mike: I didn't call the wedding off, it was her.OK, I lied.I'm sorry.
只是为了让你好过点,不,是让我自己好过点.
I did it to spare your feelings.No, I lied to spare my feelings.
凯特∶你还有什么没有跟我坦白的?
Kate: What else have you lied about?
迈克∶没有了.凯特,我很高兴我们的关系结束了,
Mike: Nothing.Kate, I am glad that relationship is over,
我也不在乎是谁甩了谁,都不重要!因为它已经是过去式了!
and I don't care who was the dumper or the dumpee, it doesn't matter!
已经结束了!我们说再见了.
It's done!It's finished!We said goodbye.
事实上,我们没有说再见,因为她只是给我写了一封愚蠢的信就离开了,
Well, we didn't actually say goodbye because she wrote me that stupid letter,
凯特,问题关键是,我爱你.
and...Look the point is...Kate, I love you.
凯特∶我也爱你,迈克.那你为什么不和她说再见?
Kate: I love you too, Mike.So, why didn't you say goodbye to her?
迈克∶跟朱莉?等等,她的姓是什么来着?别告诉我.
Mike: To Judy?Wa...w...wait, what's her name ?Don't help me.
麦琪∶明年,我来选择餐厅.
Maggie: Next year, I pick the restaurant.
杰森∶麦琪,那个沙拉酒吧有80英尺长呢.
Jason: Maggie, that salad bar was eighty feet long.
麦琪∶亲爱的,情人节的时候是不适合端着盘子排队的.
Maggie: Honey, Valentine's day is not a time to be standing in line carrying
一点也不浪漫.
a tray.It's not very romantic.
杰森∶没错,但是,我们拿了好多剩菜回来.
Jason: Yeah, well we got great left-overs.
麦琪∶亲爱的,你真的那么吝啬吗?
Maggie: Honey, are you really this cheap?
杰森∶麦琪...不.
Jason: Maggie...No.For putting up with me,
感谢你一直以来都忍受我,我知道自己在做什么,但是,
through all the times that I know what I'm doing and that one time of
有一年一次的时侯,我不会吝啬的..
year that I don't..
麦琪∶哦!...杰森杰森!
Maggie: Oh...Jason.Jason!
杰森∶情人节快乐.
Jason: Happy Valentines.
麦琪∶谢谢,太漂亮了.
Maggie: Oh...Thank you, it's beautiful.
杰森∶呵呵,他们看起来像真的钻石,不是吗?
Jason: Yeah, they look like real diamonds, don't they?
麦琪∶哦,不,他们本来就是真的.
Maggie: Oh, no, they're real.
杰森∶迈克!
Jason: Mike!
麦琪∶La Village怎么样?
Maggie: How was La Village?
杰森∶迈克!大概是还在为帐单发晕呢.
Jason: Mike!Probably still reeling from the cheque.
侍者∶先生,非常抱歉,我们已经打佯了...哦,是你.你还想来多摔一些盘子吗?
Waiter: Oh, I am terribly sorry Monsieur but we are closed...Oh, it's you.Come to break some more dishes, pally?
迈克∶啊,不是的.朱莉..朱莉卡斯提洛还在这里工作吗?她还在吗?
Mike: Ah, no.Is Julie...Julie Costello here?Is she still here?
侍者∶她的号码.
Waiter: Take a number.
迈克∶哦,哦,朱莉,你好,你好...
Mike: Oh, oh, Julie, hi, hi.Hi errm...
朱莉∶你好.
Julie: Hi.
迈克∶...,我只是回来拿点东西.
Mike: ...hi, I just came back to get my...something.
朱莉∶你的东西!
Julie: Your something!
迈克:好,我拿了,谢谢.还有,朱莉,我们可以谈谈么?
Mike: Yeah, yeah but I got it.Thanks.That's not true.Look, Julie, can we talk?
朱莉∶迈克,我现在没时间...
Julie: Mike, I really don't have time...
迈克∶谈谈!你甚至不愿意和我谈谈?
Mike: To talk!Not even to talk?
朱莉∶迈克...好吧.马上,雷.
Julie: Mike...Sure.In a minute, Ray.
雷∶呃,没问题.
Ray: Err, yeah, sure.
朱莉∶说什么?
Julie: OK, what?
迈克∶朱莉,恩...
Mike: Well, err...Well, Julie, errm...I've been thinking a lot about err...
我一直在想,
about what happened, and when I saw you over there...
到底发生了什么,
Let's just say that it's safe to say...
当我在这里看见你的时候...其实我们也没有什么事情好说的.
that, there just aren't a lot of things that need to be said, muchly.
朱莉∶迈克,现在不是我们讨论的好时机.
Julie: Mike, this just isn't a good time for us to talk.
迈克∶你又是这样!你难道都不能,不能和我说吗,朱莉?到底是什么问题?我们只差3个星期就结婚了!可是事情的结果让人觉得好笑,不是吗?也许我也应该给你写一封像你写给我的愚蠢的信.
Mike: There you go again!You can't...you can't even talk to me, Julie!What is the problem here?Look, we were three weeks away from getting married!It's funny how things turn out, isn't it?Maybe I should just have written you a stupid letter like the one you wrote me.
朱莉∶迈克,我真的很抱歉...
Julie: Mike, I am very sorry...
迈克∶如果你认为你是唯一一个对我们所做的事情有怀疑的人,那你就错了!我的怀疑比你更多!
Mike: Look, if you think you are the only one who had doubts about what we were doing Julie, you're wrong!I had better doubts!
朱莉∶当真??
Julie: Really?
迈克∶是!
Mike: You bet!
朱莉∶哦!太好了!
Julie: Oh, that's wonderful.
迈克∶你为什么要抱我?
Mike: Why are you hugging me?
朱莉:你不知道,
Julie: Well don't you see, I...
我以为我伤了你的心,可是你也怀疑,
I thought I broke your heart and I've been going around formonths just
太好了.
feeling so lousy.You had doubts too, this is great!
迈克∶真是讽刺!
Mike: Yeah, it's a real hoot!
朱莉:迈克,你为什么那么难过?你也说了你也怀疑.
Julie: Mike, why are you so upset?You just said you had the same questions.
迈克∶但是朱莉,至少在事情发生8个月后,
Mike: But Julie, at least I had the guts to come and tell you face to
我有勇气来和你面对面的谈...
face...eight months after it happened.
朱莉∶我告诉过你,我也不想写那封信的.
Julie: I told you I didn't want to write the letter.
迈克∶那么,你为什么还要写?
Mike: Well then, why did you?
朱莉∶如果我亲口告诉你,我认为结婚不是一个好的决定,
Julie: If I had told you in person that I didn't think getting married
你那时会怎么说?
was a good idea, what would you have said?
迈克∶我会说和我刚才跟你说过的一样的话.
Mike: I would have said the same things that I've said to you tonight.
朱莉∶你说的是实话吗?
Julie: Are you really being honest?
迈克∶坦白...你想要,坦白?为什么女人都要坦白?
Mike: Honest...you want, honest?OK.What is it with you women and this honesty thing?
朱莉∶迈克!
Julie: Mike!
迈克:好,我会说,不要怀疑,我们很合适.
Mike: OK, OK.OK, I would have said, that you were crazy and that you were just having cold feet...and how could this be wrong, if we were so right for each other.
朱莉∶然后我可能会深深的看着眼睛,然后我也可能会被拖垮.
Julie: And I would have looked into your eyes and I would have just crumbled.
你现在该明白我为什么写那封信了吧?
See why I wrote the letter now?
迈克∶你以为我是笨蛋,是吗?
Mike: Yeah.Guess I was a dope, huh?
朱莉∶不,你不是.你是一个有魅力的,极棒的,浪漫的...
Julie: No you weren't.You were a charming, wonderful, romantic...
迈克∶笨蛋!
Mike: Dope!
朱莉∶不会比我笨.迈克,我很开心今天晚上你能来这里.
Julie: No more than I was.I'm glad you came in here tonight, Mike.
迈克∶对,我也很开心我会回来.
Mike: Yeah, I'm glad I came back.
朱莉∶你变了.
Julie: You changed.
迈克∶没错,我长大了,明智了,诚实了.
Mike: Yeah.I'm older, wiser, honester.
朱莉∶诚实了!
Julie: Honester!
迈克∶我是改变了,还不够.好了,我要走了.
Mike: Yeah, I've changed, my hasn't.Well, err...I gotta go.
朱莉∶很高兴见到你,迈克.保重.
Julie: Good to see you, Mike, and you take care.
迈克∶再见.
Mike: Good bye.
朱莉∶再见.
Julie: Good bye.
迈克∶嘿,我们终于面对面的说再见了.
Mike: Hey, we finally said it in person.
朱莉∶是的.
Julie: Yeah.
迈克∶哦,呃...小费的事情真的不好意思.
朱莉∶什么小费?
00:21:16,200
Mike: Oh, err...sorry about the tip. Julie: What tip?